<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="changelog_style.xsl"?>
<changelog>
    <release version="12.1" versioncode="15" date="2025-09-03">
        <change>There are no Thunderbird changes requiring release notes in this release</change>
    </release>
    <release version="12.0" versioncode="14" date="2025-09-02">
        <change>Improve support for SMTPUTF8 and other UTF-8 email standards (RFC 6531, 6855)</change>
        <change>Support Android&#39;s IME autofill for password managers when adding new account</change>
        <change>Add support for avatars in account settings</change>
        <change>Enable edge-to-edge support</change>
        <change>New account settings page</change>
        <change>Long words and links in email messages did not wrap properly</change>
        <change>Swipe right to archive failed if the archive folder did not exist</change>
        <change>Edit Text dialogs in Account Settings did not automatically request focus</change>
        <change>Account Settings did not display account name</change>
        <change>In Unified Inbox, tapping a non-main account email redirected to the main inbox</change>
        <change>In dark system mode with light message theme, navigation bar was not clearly visible</change>
        <change>Threaded View toggle did not automatically update the Threaded View display</change>
        <change>Gmail prefixes were shown in the folder structure</change>
        <change>Crash could occur when adding Gmail account after removing primary Gmail account</change>
        <change>Application crashed on startup if left or right swipe gesture was set to &#39;None&#39;</change>
        <change>Crash could occur when clicking on a message thread</change>
        <change>Unicode folder names were malformed when using server supporting UTF-8</change>
        <change>Crash occurred when attempting to access account general settings</change>
        <change>Users had to manually configure Outlook IMAP and SMTP</change>
    </release>
    <release version="11.1" versioncode="13" date="2025-08-18">
        <change>Selected/read/unread message states were hard to distinguish visually</change>
    </release>
    <release version="11.0" versioncode="12" date="2025-07-14">
        <change>Improved drawer navigation with a folder hierarchy</change>
        <change>Improve dark mode emails with algorithmic darkening</change>
        <change>Welcome screen logo layout improved</change>
        <change>Improved compatibility with some ISPs by using ehlo.thunderbird.net as the EHLO identifier</change>
        <change>Selection now shown on active items by adjusting color priority</change>
        <change>Folder settings now use switches instead of checkboxes</change>
        <change>Adjust theming colors to improve contrast (message list improvements still outstanding)</change>
        <change>Messages are now marked read by default when archiving</change>
        <change>Font size config preference is removed in favor of OS and density settings</change>
        <change>Account setup issues with outlook.com and hotmail.com resolved</change>
        <change>Keyboard navigation bugs resolved</change>
        <change>Star and attachment icon colors corrected</change>
        <change>Paste of recipient lists into compose field now correctly parsed</change>
        <change>Back button now returns to Drafts folder when editing a draft</change>
        <change>Unified inbox appears when two or more accounts are configured</change>
        <change>Dark and light mode switching issues resolved</change>
        <change>Scroll indicator removed following review feedback</change>
        <change>System navigation bar did not correctly blend with message content</change>
        <change>"New Mail Notifications" setting did not persist</change>
        <change>Navigation drawer "Show Unified inbox" setting did not work</change>
        <change>Avoid crashes when selecting folders, fetching emails, adjusting accounts, or changing device orientation</change>
        <change>Sharing multiple selected images from gallery only selected last image</change>
        <change>TalkBack did not clearly announce contact picture tap action</change>
        <change>Improved IMAP push stability when switching network connections</change>
    </release>
    <release version="10.1" versioncode="11" date="2025-06-24">
        <change>Attach all images when sharing from gallery, not just the last</change>
        <change>Show the full changelog when it contains special characters</change>
    </release>
    <release version="10.0" versioncode="10" date="2025-05-05">
        <change>Server field pre-filled in manual account setup</change>
        <change>Add a menu entry to empty the Spam folder</change>
        <change>Introduce an option to use the system theme on Android 10 and older</change>
        <change>Update PushService to run as a specialUse foreground service for Android 15</change>
        <change>Update Gmail OAuth client IDs to Thunderbird for Android</change>
        <change>Preserve the &lt;s&gt; tag when sanitizing HTML content</change>
        <change>Messages and star counts in the drawer update instantly</change>
        <change>Folder names in the drawer are limited to two lines</change>
        <change>Hide accounts setting now remembered across restarts</change>
        <change>Account names in the drawer display as single lines when not set</change>
        <change>Option to use text processing apps (like Translate) when selecting text</change>
        <change>Recipient field now focused automatically when composing</change>
        <change>Display the recipient's address instead of +1 and fix its size</change>
        <change>Correct MIME type for .pkpass files</change>
        <change>Accessibility improvements</change>
        <change>Restart PushService after app update</change>
        <change>Restrict displaying message search results to internal and system usages</change>
        <change>Messages with one correspondent no longer showed "+1" incorrectly</change>
        <change>Account email no longer duplicated in drawer header</change>
    </release>
    <release version="9.0" versioncode="9" date="2025-03-03">
        <change>Basic support for Android 15</change>
        <change>Add a link to the support article when signing in with Google</change>
        <change>Account setup attempts email provider's autoconfig first, then falls back to ISPDB</change>
        <change>Updated translations for multiple languages</change>
        <change>The changelog now properly displays release versions</change>
        <change>A wrong translation of the app name has been fixed</change>
        <change>Dependencies have been updated to fix a couple of bugs</change>
    </release>
    <release version="8.2" versioncode="8" date="2024-12-09">
        <change>Account initials now use the display name</change>
        <change>Account icons remain in the same position when selected</change>
        <change>Help text linking to support page added for Gmail login issues</change>
        <change>Unified inbox enabled only when multiple accounts are configured</change>
        <change>Push service now starts reliably when expected</change>
        <change>Correct default delete message action for QR-imported accounts.</change>
        <change>Folder drawer updates properly on account configuration changes</change>
    </release>
    <release version="8.1" versioncode="5" date="2024-11-06">
        <change>Thunderbird's active development is fully funded by financial contributions from our users. If you're enjoying Thunderbird or believe in our mission, please help support it. In this version we will ask you for your support once you've had the chance to actively use Thunderbird for a while.</change>
        <change>We've fixed one of our top crashes to give you a more stable experience</change>
    </release>
    <release version="8.0" versioncode="4" date="2024-10-30">
        <change>Thunderbird for Android now looks like a Thunderbird!</change>
        <change>New folder drawer design.</change>
        <change>Migrate settings from K-9 Mail and Thunderbird Desktop within the app.</change>
        <change>Thunderbird is funded by users just like you. Contribute today, find the link in the settings.</change>
        <change>Simplified folder management by revising display and push classes.</change>
    </release>
</changelog>
